{
    "subject": "resource/Maria_Schell",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Austria",
    "human_readable": "Maria Schell was born in Austria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9850513935089111,
            "question": "Is Austria the birthplace of Maria Schell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9417853951454163,
            "question": "Did Maria Schell originate from Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9410490393638611,
            "question": "Is Maria Schell Austrian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8805051445960999,
            "question": "Maria Schell was born in what country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8612824082374573,
            "question": "Where was Maria Schell born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8198213577270508,
            "question": "In which region was Maria Schell born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.730651319026947,
            "question": "What is the birthplace of Maria Schell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5360560417175293,
            "question": "Can you tell me Maria Schell's place of birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5168270468711853,
            "question": "What country is Maria Schell from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4326709508895874,
            "question": "Where did Maria Schell hail from?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Maria Schell was born in Austria.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2818_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Maria Schell from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2818_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me Maria Schell's place of birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2818_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the birthplace of Maria Schell?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2818_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2818_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2818_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2818_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2818_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2818_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2818_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2818_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2818_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2818_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2818_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nExplanation: The documents mention that Maria Schell was born on January 15, 1926, in Vienna, Austria. This supports the statement that Maria Schell was born in Austria."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}